{
    "subject": "resource/Frederick_Belson",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Frederick Charles Belson (13 February 1874 \u2013 10 August 1952) was an English international rugby union forward who played club rugby for Clifton and Bath, and county rugby for Somerset. Belson played international rugby for the British Isles on their 1899 tour of Australia.",
    "human_readable": "Frederick Charles Belson was an English international rugby union forward who played club rugby for Clifton and Bath, and county rugby for Somerset, as well as playing international rugby for the British Isles on their 1899 tour of Australia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9748952388763428,
            "question": "For which English county did Frederick Charles Belson play rugby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9707666039466858,
            "question": "Name the two clubs for which Frederick Charles Belson played club rugby."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9657312035560608,
            "question": "Was Frederick Charles Belson involved in international rugby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9650627374649048,
            "question": "Which clubs did Frederick Charles Belson play club rugby for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9599887132644653,
            "question": "Where did Frederick Charles Belson go on a rugby tour in 1899?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9464825987815857,
            "question": "What position did Frederick Charles Belson play in rugby union?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9283948540687561,
            "question": "In what year did Frederick Charles Belson tour Australia with the British Isles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9237712621688843,
            "question": "What is known about Frederick Charles Belson's role in rugby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.848088264465332,
            "question": "Besides playing club rugby, what other level of rugby did Frederick Charles Belson participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7836839556694031,
            "question": "What was Frederick Charles Belson's nationality?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frederick Charles Belson was an English international rugby union forward who played club rugby for Clifton and Bath, and county rugby for Somerset, as well as playing international rugby for the British Isles on their 1899 tour of Australia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5389_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides playing club rugby, what other level of rugby did Frederick Charles Belson participate in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5389_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Frederick Charles Belson's role in rugby?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5389_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Frederick Charles Belson tour Australia with the British Isles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5389_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5389_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5389_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5389_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5389_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5389_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5389_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5389_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5389_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5389_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5389_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. Frederick Charles Belson is mentioned to have played rugby for Bath, Somerset, Bristol, Clifton, and Abergavenny (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5389/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt). He is also mentioned to be a member of the Anglo Australian Tour party in 1899, which was a precursor to the British Lions (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5389/re-ranker-msmarco/42.txt). This information aligns with the statement that he played international rugby for the British Isles on their 1899 tour of Australia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents support that Frederick Charles Belson was an English international rugby union forward who played club rugby for Clifton and Bath, and county rugby for Somerset. The information also confirms his participation in the British Isles' tour of Australia in 1899."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}